import { UnderlineText,
    UnderlineText2, SquareRoot, superscript, subscript, BoldText, ItalicText, Fraction, ShortFraction, LongFraction, MixedFraction, Isotopes } from "@/mathnotation"



export const ENGLISHLANGUAGEA2000 = [

{
section: "1",
instruction: "In each of the following sentence, there is one word or group of words underlined word and one gap. From the list of words or group of words lettered A to D, choose the one that is most nearly opposite in meaning to the underlined word or group of words and that will, at the same time, correctly fill the gap in the sentence.",
id: "question1",
question: ["1. Hello Musa' is a. opening for a friendly letter, but it is ", <UnderlineText key={"1"} text={"inappropriate"}/>, " for a formal letter."],
A: "casual",
B: "serious",
C: "happy",
D: "suitable",
answer: "D. suitable",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question2",
question: ["2. We ", <UnderlineText key={"2"} text={"blamed"}/>, "Obi for breaking the door, but when Ade confessed that he did it, Obi was. ."],
A: "exonerated",
B: "exonerated",
C: "released",
D: "jailed.",
answer: "B. exonerated",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question3",
question: ["3. Parking on this street is.... on weekdays but ", <UnderlineText key={"3"} text={"permitted"}/>, "at weekends."],
A: "rejected",
B: "sanctioned",
C: "abolished",
D: "prohibited.",
answer: "D. prohibited",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question4",
question: ["4. They had to _________ the old building to ", <UnderlineText key={"4"} text={"construct"}/>, " the five-star hotel."],
A: "close",
B: "remove",
C: "demolish",
D: "damage",
answer: "C. demolish",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question5",
question: ["5. If we can ", <UnderlineText key={"5"} text={"commence"}/>, " the meeting on time, we should be able to ____________ by 4.00 p.m."],
A: "return",
B: "vacate",
C: "convene",
D: "adjourn.",
answer: "D. adjourn",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question6",
question: ["6. The children were expected to be ", <UnderlineText key={"6"} text={"praised"}/>, " for putting out the fire, but they were _________ for taking such a risk."],
A: "rebuked",
B: "accused",
C: "despised",
D: "sentenced.",
answer: "A. rebuked",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question7",
question: ["7. A child got ", <UnderlineText key={"7"} text={"stuck"}/>, "trying to squeeze through an iron fence, but some adults managed to _________ him."],
A: "extract",
B: "push",
C: "save",
D: "extricate.",
answer: "D. extricate",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question8",
question: ["8. They ended the discussion on ", <UnderlineText key={"5"} text={"amicable"}/>, " terms though they were _________ to each other at the beginning."],
A: "unacceptable",
B: "hostile",
C: "unknown",
D: "annoying.",
answer: "B. hostile",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
section: "2",
instruction: "From the words lettered A to D, choose the word that best completes each of the following sentences.",
id: "question9",
question: "9. The class prefect's _______ of the quarrel is different from yours.",
A: "statement",
B: "account",
C: "outline",
D: "summary.",
answer: "B. account",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question10",
question: "10. I refused to _______ my statement because it was true",
A: "retract",
B: "make",
C: "witssold",
D: "voice.",
answer: "A. retract",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question11",
question: "11. But for the timely _________ of the police, there would have been a riot.",
A: "interference",
B: "intrusion",
C: "intervention",
D: "interruption.",
answer: "C. intervention",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question12",
question: "12. The boys were about to trade blows, but I managed to hold one of them back while my friend ________ the other",
A: "restrained",
B: "subdued",
C: "coaxed",
D: "captured.",
answer: "A. restrained",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question13",
question: "13. We are waiting to hear the weather ________ for tomorrow.",
A: "broadcast",
B: "declaration",
C: "report",
D: "forecast.",
answer: "D. forecast",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question14",
question: "14. I will tell you the secret if you promise not to ____________ _________ it.",
A: "divulge",
B: "show",
C: "scatter",
D: "relay.",
answer: "A. divulge",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question15",
question: "15. The hilltop was a hundred metres above sea level and from that _________ the whole town could be seen beautifully laid out.",
A: "magnitude",
B: "altitude",
C: "latitude",
D: "longitude.",
answer: "B. altitude",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question16",
question: "16. Until now Etim has always started the fights, but this time Adamu is clearly the __________ ",
A: "oppressor",
B: "fighter",
C: "aggressor",
D: "underdog",
answer: "C. aggressor",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question17",
question: "17. If found guilty, a person may appeal to a higher court in the hope that it will ________ the verdict.",
A: "discharge",
B: "revise",
C: "dismiss",
D: "reverse.",
answer: "D. reverse",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question18",
question: "18. The visit of the patron of the club _________ the morale of the players.",
A: "elated",
B: "induced",
C: "boasted",
D: "boosted",
answer: "D. boosted",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
section: "3",
instruction: "After each of the following sentences, a list of possible interpretations is given. Choose the interpretation that you consider most appropriate for each sentence.",
id: "question19",
question: "19. Although Aliyu was acquitted by the court for want of evidence, the police still kept a tab on him. This means that they ___________",
A: "kept him under close observation.",
B: "set a trap to catch him again.",
C: "attached a tag to his clothes.",
D: "kept him behind bars.",
answer: "A. kept him under close observation",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question20",
question: "20. When it came to the question of an increase in allowances, the striking workers spoke with one voice. This means that the workers ___________",
A: "became frightened",
B: "appointed one of them as their Spokesman.",
C: "repeated their demand in a chorus",
D: "were unanimous in their position.",
answer: "D. were unanimous in their position",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question21",
question: "21. The restaurant owner offered Olu a drink on the house. This means that. ___________",
A: "the drink was taken to Olu's house.",
B: "Olu was invited to the owner's house",
C: "the drink was free of charge.",
D: "Olu was served inside the restaurant.",
answer: "C. the drink was free of charge",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question22",
question: "22. When the Choir Master introduced Jane as a brilliant singer, everyone knew that he was speaking with his tongue in his cheek. This means that he ___________",
A: "was ignorant of the quality of Jane's singing",
B: "did not intend to be taken seriously.",
C: "wanted to deceive Jane",
D: "wanted to deceived everyone but failed.",
answer: "B. did not intend to be taken seriously",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question23",
question: "23. When the accountant made those remarks he knew that he was putting his job on the line. This means that the accountant was.",
A: "risking",
B: "announcing his resignation.",
C: "urging people to take to his profession.",
D: "revealing secrets about his job.",
answer: "A. risking",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question24",
question: "24. The newly acquired air-bus plane is a white elephant. This means that the plane is ___________",
A: "very costly but worthless.",
B: "very useful",
C: "as big as an elephant.",
D: "the biggest plane on the fleet.",
answer: "A. very costly but worthless",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question25",
question: "25. Despite the measures taken by the government, the economy of the country is still in the doldrums. This means that ___________",
A: "the economy is recovering.",
B: "the government tackling the problem vigorously.",
C: "the economic problems are widely known",
D: "the economy is not making any progress.",
answer: "D. the economy is not making any progress",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question26",
question: "26. The new teacher urged the lazy students to turn a new leaf. This means that the teacher urged the students to ___________",
A: "improve their behaviour",
B: "turn to the next page of their book.",
C: "stir the leaf in the compost pit",
D: "strike a balance between play and hard work",
answer: "A. improve their behaviour",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question27",
question: "27. Amina always flies off at a tangent when a serious matter is being discussed. This means that Amina ___________",
A: "gets over-excited.",
B: "keeps digressing.",
C: "keeps the discussion lively.",
D: "has nothing to contribute.",
answer: "B. keeps digressing",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question28",
question: "28. You should take what he tells you with a pinch of salt. This means that you should ___________",
A: "reject everything he says because he is a liar.",
B: "pay close attention to him",
C: "doubt what he says",
D: "question him closely.",
answer: "C. doubt what he says",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
section: "4",
instruction: "From the wordh lettered A. to D below each of the following sentences, choose the word that is noarost in moaning to the underlined word ah it is uhed in the sentence.",
id: "question29",
question: ["29. The bride was praised by her mother-in law for her ", <UnderlineText key={"5"} text={"impeccable"}/>, " behaviour."],
A: "spotless",
B: "appropriate",
C: "beautiful",
D: "faultless",
answer: "D. faultless",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question30",
question: ["30. Ogene was not the least ", <UnderlineText key={"5"} text={"cowed"}/>, " by the bully's threats."],
A: "frightened",
B: "worried",
C: "encouraged",
D: "distracted",
answer: "A. frightened",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question31",
question: ["31. The dissidents held several ", <UnderlineText key={"5"} text={"clandestine"}/>, " meetings before the attack."],
A: "secret",
B: "important",
C: "impromptu",
D: "exclusive",
answer: "A. secret",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question32",
question: ["32. The principal warned the final-students about the consequences of ", <UnderlineText key={"5"} text={"procastination"}/>, ],
A: "haste",
B: "delay",
C: "protesting",
D: "rioting.",
answer: "B. delay",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question33",
question: ["33. The incessant chatter of the pupils ", <UnderlineText key={"5"} text={"irritates"}/>, " the teacher."],
A: "excited",
B: "meaningless",
C: "unceasing",
D: "illogical.",
answer: "C. unceasing",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question34",
question: ["34. With his ", <UnderlineText key={"5"} text={"cogent"}/>, " argument in favour of the proposal he was able to check further opposition."],
A: "insistent.",
B: "urgent",
C: "convincing",
D: "uncompromising",
answer: "C. convincing",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question35",
question: ["35. The professor's explanation of that point was quite ", <UnderlineText key={"5"} text={"lucid."}/>, ],
A: "lengthy",
B: "complicated",
C: "clear",
D: "surprising.",
answer: "C. clear",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question36",
question: ["36. The foreman believed that with the ", <UnderlineText key={"5"} text={"augmented"}/>, " workforce, the construction, job would take one more month to complete."],
A: "skilled",
B: "enlarged",
C: "hired",
D: "determined",
answer: "B. enlarged",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question37",
question: ["37. The children were warned not to be unduly ", <UnderlineText key={"5"} text={"inquisitive"}/>, "."],
A: "naughty",
B: "playful",
C: "troublesome",
D: "curious",
answer: "D. curious",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
section: "5",
instruction: "Form the wordh or group of wordh lettered A to D, choose the word or group of wordh that bost complotos each of the following sentences:",
id: "question39",
question: "39. The man advised his children not to give _________ to the temptation of the city.",
A: "off",
B: "up.",
C: "in",
D: "on",
answer: "C. off",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question39",
question: "39. Let us keep ________ the plans we made earlier.",
A: "away",
B: "to",
C: "off",
D: "on",
answer: "C. off",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question40",
question: "40. Ebiere turned ___________ the advances made by the man.",
A: "aside",
B: "off",
C: "away",
D: "down",
answer: "D. down",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question41",
question: "41. Ada is ___________ to do that kind of thing",
A: "too intelligent much",
B: "too much intelligent",
C: "intelligent too much",
D: "much too intelligent",
answer: "B. too much intelligent",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question42",
question: "42. __________ were sent to the library by the English teacher.",
A: "I and Udoh",
B: "Udoh and me",
C: "Udoh and I",
D: "myself and Udoh.",
answer: "C. Udoh and I",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question43",
question: "43. The teachers ___________ politics when I entered the staff room.",
A: "are discussing",
B: "were discussing about",
C: "are discussing on",
D: "were discussing.",
answer: "D. were discussing",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question44",
question: "44. The quarrel between the two men soon resulted ___________ a fight.",
A: "to",
B: "in",
C: "towards",
D: "into.",
answer: "B. in",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question45",
question: "45. You're not too tired to continue, ___________ ?",
A: "are you",
B: "isn't it",
C: "can't you",
D: "is it.",
answer: "A. are you",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question46",
question: "46. The hunter, with his dog, _________ going into the forest",
A: "was seen",
B: "are being seen",
C: "have been seen",
D: "were seen",
answer: "A. was seen",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question47",
question: "47. Mother could not prepare the dish because there was _________ oil available.",
A: "small",
B: "little",
C: "a little",
D: "some.",
answer: "C. a little",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question48",
question: "48. Because it had been raining heavily all morning, _________ people turned out to welcome the august visitor.",
A: "few",
B: "quite a few",
C: "only fewer",
D: "a few",
answer: "A. few",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question49",
question: "49. Unfortunately, his plans to go abroad fell ___________",
A: "off",
B: "down",
C: "under",
D: "through",
answer: "D. through",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question50",
question: "50. The man asked me ___________",
A: "who am I?",
B: "that who are you?",
C: "who I am?",
D: "who I was?",
answer: "C. who I am?",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question51",
question: "51. It is high time you __________ crying, the woman told her daughter gently.",
A: "stop",
B: "should stop",
C: "stopped",
D: "must stop.",
answer: "C. stopped",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question52",
question: "52. He would rather resign __________ part in such a dishonest deal.",
A: "instead of taking",
B: "than taking",
C: "than takes",
D: "than take.",
answer: "B. than taking",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question53",
question: "53. Those who own the company were urged to ____________ their debts.",
A: "make good",
B: "pay out",
C: "run in",
D: "pay for.",
answer: "B. pay out",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question54",
question: "54. _____________ home, his dead uncle's burial had already taken place.",
A: "Getting",
B: "As he gets",
C: "On getting",
D: "When he got.",
answer: "C. On getting",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question55",
question: "55. Luck _________ the robbers on that fateful day.",
A: "come down on",
B: "ran out on",
C: "ended up with",
D: "made away with.",
answer: "B. ran out on",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question56",
question: "56. He never seemed to get it wrong ____________",
A: "however he hard",
B: "he tried hard however",
C: "he however tried hard",
D: "however hard he tried.",
answer: "D. however hard he tried",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question57",
question: "57. The day that Musa's uncle died was the __________ day of his life.",
A: "more sadder",
B: "sadder",
C: "saddest",
D: "most saddest.",
answer: "C. saddest",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question58",
question: "58. With his reading glasses on, he could see the words ______________ ",
A: "much more clearly",
B: "clearly much more",
C: "much clearly more",
D: "much more clearer.",
answer: "A. much more clearly",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question59",
question: "59. Neither Obi nor Jumoke _________ present at the meeting.",
A: "was",
B: "were",
C: "have been",
D: "are",
answer: "A. was",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question60",
question: "60. Hardly had the journey started ____________ the car engine developeda fault.",
A: "that",
B: "when",
C: "than",
D: "soon",
answer: "B. when",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question61",
question: "61. At the end of this year, grandmother ____________ with us for seven years.",
A: "is living",
B: "has lived",
C: "will have lived",
D: "has been living",
answer: "C. will have lived",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question62",
question: "62. One of the robbers who snatched the car _________ been arrested by the police.",
A: "have",
B: "was",
C: "is",
D: "has",
answer: "D. has",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question63",
question: "63. A student at the back of the class complained that he _________ the teacher.",
A: "was not hearing B.",
C: "does not hear",
D: "is not hearing",
answer: "B. could not hear",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question64",
question: "64. The little boy could not move the heavy stone _________ he tried.",
A: "as much as",
B: "how much",
C: "no matter that",
D: "has been living",
answer: "A. as much as",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question65",
question: "65. The two girls have not been speaking _________ since their quarrel.",
A: "one to the other",
B: "to themselves",
C: "to each another",
D: "to each other.",
answer: "D. to each other",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question66",
question: "66. We received ____________ that the workers would soon go on strike.",
A: "an information",
B: "information’s",
C: "those information",
D: "information.",
answer: "D. information",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question67",
question: "67. He dabbles ________ politics from time to time.",
A: "in",
B: "with",
C: "through",
D: "into",
answer: "A. in",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question68",
question: "68. The government has set up a _________ panel to investigate the fire incident",
A: "five-men",
B: "five men",
C: "five-man",
D: "five man",
answer: "C. five-man",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question69",
question: "69. The students' week was rounded ____________ with a dance.",
A: "off",
B: "up",
C: "out",
D: "through.",
answer: "A. off",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question70",
question: "70. The factory workers refused to take the matter of their sacked colleagues lying _____________",
A: "low",
B: "low",
C: "down",
D: "idle.",
answer: "C. down",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question71",
question: "71. After a while, we noticed that the unconscious accident victim was coming _____________",
A: "round",
B: "on",
C: "low",
D: "down",
answer: "A. round",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question72",
question: "72. Seun accepted the conditions we gave him ____________ for my liking.",
A: "quickly too much",
B: "too much quickly",
C: "much too quickly",
D: "much quickly too",
answer: "B. too much quickly",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question73",
question: "73. The careless manager has caused his bank to _________ millions of dollars.",
A: "loose",
B: "losing",
C: "lose",
D: "lost.",
answer: "C. lose",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question74",
question: "74. Both questions are alternatives: you answer ___________ one ____________ the other.",
A: "neither, nor",
B: "both and",
C: "neither, or",
D: "either, or.",
answer: "D. either, or",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question75",
question: "75. The sick man _________ in bed for three months.",
A: "lay",
B: "lain",
C: "lied",
D: "lie.",
answer: "A. lay",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question76",
question: "76. Ogugua has always ____________ me as good mannered child",
A: "strike",
B: "struck",
C: "stricken",
D: "striking",
answer: "B. struck",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
section: "6",
instruction: "In the following passageh, the numbered gaph indicate missing wordh. Against each number in the list below each passage, four options are given in columns lettered A, to D. Choose the word that is the moht huitable to fill the numbered gaph in the passageh.",
passage: "For thousands of years, men lived in a very primitive way. Before the recent -77- in agriculture, medicine and industry, life was difficult. It was hard to -78- living from the -79- without modern farming -80- and a single year of crop -81- could mean famine and therefore death. Ilnesses as -82- and as -83- as influenza could kill a Stone-Age man weakened by hunger; appendicitis was always - 84- before the days of modern -85-. Even childbirth was a hazardous process. Under these Conditions. The human race needed to -86- at a high -87-just to keep in existence. However, with a sharp fall in the -88- rate relative to the -89-, the world's population is now ncreasing very rapidly. This increase needs to be put in -90-to avo1d the looming consequence of population -91-.",
id: "question77",
question: "77. *********************",
A: "developments",
B: "growths",
C: "adventures",
D: "experiments",
answer: "A. developments",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question78",
question: "78. *********************",
A: "get",
B: "realize",
C: "make",
D: "extract",
answer: "C. make",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question79",
question: "79. *********************",
A: "ground",
B: "soil",
C: "world",
D: "earth",
answer: "B. soil",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question80",
question: "80. *********************",
A: "methods",
B: "procedures",
C: "steps",
D: "ways",
answer: "A. methods",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question81",
question: "81. *********************",
A: "collapse",
B: "withdrawal",
C: "decease",
D: "failure",
answer: "D. failure",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question82",
question: "82. *********************",
A: "meek",
B: "withdrawal",
C: "mild",
D: "benign",
answer: "C. mild",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question83",
question: "83. *********************",
A: "common",
B: "ubiquitous",
C: "omnipresent",
D: "numerous",
answer: "A. common",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question84",
question: "84. *********************",
A: "vanquished",
B: "fatal",
C: "killing",
D: "deathly",
answer: "B. fatal",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question85",
question: "85. *********************",
A: "medication",
B: "counselling",
C: "therapy",
D: "surgery",
answer: "A. medication",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question86",
question: "86. *********************",
A: "recreate",
B: "replenish",
C: "reproduce",
D: "recycle",
answer: "C. reproduce",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question87",
question: "87. *********************",
A: "speed",
B: "rate",
C: "pace",
D: "frequency",
answer: "B. rate",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question88",
question: "88. *********************",
A: "maternity",
B: "morality",
C: "paternity",
D: "mortality",
answer: "D. mortality",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question89",
question: "89. *********************",
A: "birth-rate",
B: "living",
C: "healthy",
D: "women",
answer: "A. birth-rate",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question90",
question: "90. *********************",
A: "detention",
B: "bondage",
C: "check",
D: "reverse",
answer: "C. check",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question91",
question: "91. *********************",
A: "enlargement",
B: "explosion",
C: "bank",
D: "expansion",
answer: "B. explosion",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
passage: "When my elder brother decided to -92- a current account with the United Bank for Africa, he walked into one of its -93- and obtained the necessary -94-which he completed and retuned to the 95-. He was then given paying-in -96-. Soon, he started issuing -97- to people with whom he transacted business. Whenever his signature was irregular, his cheque was not -98-. Once, he wanted to obtain a -99-, and the bank insisted on -100-",
id: "question92",
question: "92. *********************",
A: "start",
B: "open",
C: "begin",
D: "close",
answer: "B. open",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question93",
question: "93. *********************",
A: "branches",
B: "offices",
C: "premises",
D: "houses",
answer: "A. branches",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question94",
question: "94. *********************",
A: "bills",
B: "booklets",
C: "applications",
D: "forms",
answer: "D. forms",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question95",
question: "95. *********************",
A: "principal",
B: "director",
C: "manager",
D: "chairman.",
answer: "C. manager",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question96",
question: "96. *********************",
A: "papers",
B: "bonds",
C: "tallies",
D: "slips",
answer: "D. slips",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question97",
question: "97. *********************",
A: "cheques",
B: "money",
C: "numbers",
D: "contracts",
answer: "A. cheques",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question98",
question: "98. *********************",
A: "accepted",
B: "honoured",
C: "paid",
D: "received",
answer: "B. honoured",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question99",
question: "99. *********************",
A: "credit",
B: "debit",
C: "loan",
D: "balance",
answer: "C. loan",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question100",
question: "100. *********************",
A: "a witness",
B: "a guarantor",
C: "collateral",
D: "interest",
answer: "C. collateral",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},



]